<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Odyssey346</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Odyssey346</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2022 - present Odyssey346.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:05:04 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//odyssey346.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A new theme.. again?</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newthemeagain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 15:05:04 +0100</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newthemeagain/</guid><description>So yes, I switched themes again. This is the second time! This time I made it from scratch. It&amp;rsquo;s called &amp;ldquo;Cardio&amp;rdquo;, because it has a paper layout. Also because it&amp;rsquo;s trimmed of fat.
Why new theme, and why not use a pre-existing one? I wanted to learn Hugo some more, since I&amp;rsquo;m genuinely interested in the Hugo CMS. What better way than to make a Hugo theme? I was also not satisfied with the old theme.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Frontends on Odyssey346.dev</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/selfhost/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 22:25:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/selfhost/</guid><description>Privacy and bandwidth are important. This is true. All those services like YouTube load an insane amount of bloat in your browser. All you want to do is watch a YouTube video? Enjoy like 10MB of JS, HTML, tracking etc. You agree that sucks, right? Well, you have Invidious and Piped, which let you watch YouTube videos, without all the tracking and bloat. Same applies to Reddit, which has a privacy frontend called Libreddit.</description></item><item><title>Getting Minecraft to run on a legacy Intel iGPU with Adoptium/Temurin JRE</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/adoptiumopengl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:44:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/adoptiumopengl/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; why? I was checking out my ThinkPad, and I was trying to run Minecraft on it. To my surprise, apparently it did not support OpenGL! But, it does support OpenGL&amp;hellip; what&amp;rsquo;s going on?
Let&amp;rsquo;s blame Intel Intel&amp;rsquo;s graphic drivers were, obviously, legacy. This is a laptop from 2012. The drivers weren&amp;rsquo;t intended to run on Windows 10, but it does&amp;hellip; here&amp;rsquo;s where it messes up though: Windows 10 and newer change the NT kernel version from 6 to 10.</description></item><item><title>New Theme!</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newtheme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:24:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newtheme/</guid><description>New Theme for the blog! I was happy with the old theme but I like the Hello Friend theme. I liked the layout, but the theme, was ehh.. So I forked it! So the current theme have my changes. Light mode is a bit scuffed at the moment, but hey, it works.
Thoughts? Well, there is a comment section right under here. Post your thoughts about the theme there, and any bugs/inconsistencies you find in it :)</description></item><item><title>Delete your old internet past</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:14:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/delete/</guid><description>My experience getting my information off of the Internet Recently I decided to learn about tools you can use to stalk find out information about Internet users, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been using them to find information I&amp;rsquo;ve published about myself on the internet that I really shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have. So, in this post I will show off the tools I used and my technique to finding information about myself that I&amp;rsquo;ve published on the internet, and find old accounts, so that you can stay safe on the internet.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:07:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>This blog (and new site) meets the Internet. Blog + New Site combined! I&amp;rsquo;m experimenting with Hugo now. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if it works out or not!</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/about/</guid><description>Well, who am I I&amp;rsquo;m a 15 year old Norwegian computer nerd who enjoys tinkering with code and software. I also like playing games. I sound really generic, don&amp;rsquo;t I? Maybe cause I am.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of my personality, in audio format:
Seems like playing audio isn't supported in your browser. What I&amp;rsquo;ve done and made I&amp;rsquo;ve:
been in 3 organizations dabbling with computers. (Terrific Tea Studios, Neutron Technologies, Project Segfault) made a tool called Fixdows (now private) lived for 14 years (amazing accomplishment) Probably some more things I forgot.</description></item><item><title>My email</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/mail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/mail/</guid><description>Well, like most people, I have an email address. My e-mail address is hi@odyssey346.dev. I have other e-mail addresses, but I primarily use this one for contact.</description></item></channel></rss>