<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Odyssey346</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/</link><description>Recent content on Odyssey346</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2022 - present Odyssey346.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:44:44 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//odyssey346.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Minecraft to run on a legacy Intel iGPU with Adoptium/Temurin JRE</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/adoptiumopengl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:44:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/adoptiumopengl/</guid><description>
So&amp;hellip; why? # I was checking out my ThinkPad, and I was trying to run Minecraft on it. To my surprise, apparently it did not support OpenGL! But, it does support OpenGL&amp;hellip; what&amp;rsquo;s going on?
Let&amp;rsquo;s blame Intel # Intel&amp;rsquo;s graphic drivers were, obviously, legacy. This is a laptop from 2012. The drivers weren&amp;rsquo;t intended to run on Windows 10, but it does&amp;hellip; here&amp;rsquo;s where it messes up though: Windows 10 and newer change the NT kernel version from 6 to 10.</description></item><item><title>New Theme!</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newtheme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:24:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/newtheme/</guid><description>
New Theme for the blog! # I was happy with the old theme but I like the Hello Friend theme. I liked the layout, but the theme, was ehh.. So I forked it! So the current theme have my changes. Light mode is a bit scuffed at the moment, but hey, it works.
Thoughts? # Well, there is a comment section right under here. Post your thoughts about the theme there, and any bugs/inconsistencies you find in it :)</description></item><item><title>My Specs</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/my-specs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 20:34:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/my-specs/</guid><description>
I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be fun to make a post about my computers specs. Here you go, to those interested.
My main rig&amp;rsquo;s specs # CPU: AMD Ryzen 7 2700x GPU: Asus Dual GeForce GTX 1060 OC (6GB) RAM: Corsair Vengeance RGB PRO DDR4 3600MHz CL18 16GB NVMe Drive: Samsung 980 500GB SSD: Kingston A400 980GB HDD: Seagate Barracuda 3TB 3.5&amp;quot; HDD (5400 RPM) Case: Cooler Master Trooper SE Motherboard: ASUS ROG STRIX B450-F GAMING PSU: Corsair RM1000X 1000W PSU Main rig, but not computer related # Mouse: MX Master 3 Keyboard: Corsair K95 RGB Platinum XT Headset: SteelSeries Arctis 5 (Black) VR Headset: Oculus Quest 2 128GB VR Cable: Random ass cheap 3 meter long USB3 cable Operating System: Windows 11 Enterprise activated using MAS</description></item><item><title>Delete your old internet past</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:14:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/delete/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="//odyssey346.dev/images/sherlock.png"/>
My experience getting my information off of the Internet # Recently I decided to learn about tools you can use to stalk find out information about Internet users, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been using them to find information I&amp;rsquo;ve published about myself on the internet that I really shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have. So, in this post I will show off the tools I used and my technique to finding information about myself that I&amp;rsquo;ve published on the internet, and find old accounts, so that you can stay safe on the internet.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:07:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>
This blog (and new site) meets the internet. # Blog + New Site combined! # I&amp;rsquo;m experimenting with Hugo now. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if it works out or not!</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/about/</guid><description>
Well, who am I # I&amp;rsquo;m a 14 year old Norwegian computer nerd who enjoys tinkering with code and software. I also like playing games. I sound really generic, don&amp;rsquo;t I? Maybe cause I am.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of my personality, in audio format:
Seems like playing audio isn't supported in your browser. What I&amp;rsquo;ve done and made # I&amp;rsquo;ve:
been in 3 organizations dabbling with computers. (Terrific Tea Studios, Neutron Technologies, Project Segfault) made a tool called Fixdows lived for 14 years (amazing accomplishment) Probably some more things I forgot.</description></item><item><title>My email</title><link>//odyssey346.dev/mail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//odyssey346.dev/mail/</guid><description>
Well, like most people, I have an email address. # My e-mail address is odyssey346@disroot.org. I have other e-mail addresses than this one, but this is the one I&amp;rsquo;d like you to use.
If you need my public key, here it is.</description></item></channel></rss>